{
    "id": "51a39b9934ab4c00ab13ffda633c40be",
    "title": "Subject verb agreement exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c82be77a58444a439445c8ba21ba9d49",
            "title": "Subject Verb Agreement",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Man and woman ………………… complementary to each other.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Plenty of mangoes and bananas ………………… available in this season.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A dictionary and an atlas …………………… missing from the library.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The leader as well as his brothers ………………… to the same tribe.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "belong",
                        "belongs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cats and dogs ……………….…….. not get along.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The brothers as well as their sister …………………… .. good at their studies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The students accompanied by their teacher …………………. gone on a picnic.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A lot of houses ………………… collapsed in the storm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children as well as their mother …………………. missing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A large sum of money ………………… stolen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}